proxylist.co 2015-05-26

# Privacy Policy

[box style=”green” title=”How ProxyList.co Uses Your Personal Information”]This policy covers how ProxyList.co treats personal information that ProxyList.co collects and receives, including information related to your past use of ProxyList.co products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.[/box] [box style=”green” title=”This privacy policy only applies to ProxyList.co”]This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that ProxyList.co does not own or control, or to people that ProxyList.co does not employ or manage. In addition, some companies that ProxyList.co has acquired have their own, preexisting privacy policies which may be viewed on our acquired companies page.[/box] [box style=”green” title=”INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE”]ProxyList.co collects personal information when you register with ProxyList.co, when you use ProxyList.co services, when you visit ProxyList.co pages or the pages of certain ProxyList.co partners. ProxyList.co may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, and basic information. When you register with ProxyList.co and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

ProxyList.co automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, ProxyList.co cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.

ProxyList.co uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.[/box] [box style=”green” title=”INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE”]ProxyList.co does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ProxyList.co’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if ProxyList.co is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, ProxyList.co will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

ProxyList.co works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business.[/box] [box style=”green” title=”COOKIES AND TRAFFIC DATA”]ProxyList.co may set and access ProxyList.co cookies on your computer. In additional, ProxyList.co uses cookies and tracking technologies to estimate and report the total audience size and traffic; accumulate and report aggregated statistical information about ProxyList.co site and advertisement usage; keep count of return visits to our site, determine our users interests and keep track of preferences you specify while you are using ProxyList.co services.[/box] [box style=”green” title=”COMMUNICATION”]We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the ProxyList.co service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the ProxyList.co Newsletter, that are considered part of your ProxyList.co account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.[/box] [box style=”green” title=”CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY”]ProxyList.co may update this privacy policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your ProxyList.co account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.[/box] [box style=”green” title=”CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY”]ProxyList.co may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your ProxyList.co account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.[/box] [box style=”green” title=”QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS”]If you have any specific questions about this privacy policy, please feel free to contact us directly.[/box]
